Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series X: Audio-Visual Material, 1957-2009; 448922
  - Subseries X:A: Audio Cassettes, 1968-2009; 448923
    - Howard Zinn: Interview on "A Break-in for Peace," Article on the Camden 28 Published in The Progressive (July 2002), Jul 22, 2002; cuid17244; 449763 (Box 74, Cassette 138)
    - WBUR / NPR: The Connection - "Where's the Opposition?: The Left's Position on the Iraq War" (includes Peter Lems, Leo Ribuffo and Congresswoman Barbara Lee), Sep 17, 2002; cuid17245; 449764 (Box 74, Cassette 139)
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn - Interview (Stony Brook, NY), May 19, 2003; cuid17246; 449765 (Box 74, Cassette 140)
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn - Interview (Stony Brook, NY), Mar 28, 2005; cuid17247; 449766 (Box 74, Cassette 141)
    - WAMU: Howard Zinn Interviewed by Diane Rehm on Voices of a People's History of the United States (American University, Washington, DC), May 2, 2005; cuid17248; 449767 (Box 74, Cassette 142)
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn - Interview on A Power Governments Cannot Suppress (Stony Brook, NY), Jan 20, 2007; cuid17249; 449768 (Box 74, Cassette 143)
    - KVSC Newswatch: Howard Zinn Interview on Voices of a People's History of the United States, Dec 13, 2009; cuid17250; 449769 (Box 74, Cassette 144)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Race and Law, Oct 12; cuid17251; 449770 (Box 74, Cassette 145)
      Tape was slated to be digitized in 2015 but could not be due to binder hydrolysis. It was kept for incubation and baking, but transfer was unsuccessful as of 2017.
    - Dial a Radio: Howard Zinn - Interview (also includes music and other interviews), undated; cuid17252; 449771 (Box 74, Cassette 146)
    - Diane Valcourt's Audio Journal for Howard Zinn (PO 394), undated; cuid17253; 449772 (Box 74, Cassette 147)
    - Documentary on Emma Goldman, undated; cuid17254; 449775 (Box 74, Cassette 148)
    - Emma: A Play in Two Acts about Emma Goldman, American Anarchist by Howard Zinn: Performance in French, undated; cuid17255; 449773 (Box 74, Cassette 149)
    - Eqbal Ahmed on Progressive Movements in Pakistan Tape 4, undated; cuid17256; 449774 (Box 74, Cassette 150)
    - "Freedom and Democracy": Spoken Word by Howard Zinn and Music by Steve Lutke and James Voris, undated; cuid17257; 449776 (Box 74, Cassette 151)
    - "Freedom and Democracy": Spoken Word by Howard Zinn and Music by Steve Lutke and James Voris, undated; cuid17258; 449777 (Box 74, Cassette 151 dup)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Bacon's Rebellion (poor audio quality), undated; cuid17259; 449778 (Box 74, Cassette 152)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Central America and Just and Unjust Wars, undated; cuid17260; 449779 (Box 74, Cassette 153)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Civil Disobedience Versus Voting (Tactics) / Bill Baird: Lecture to Howard Zinn's Class / Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Daniel Berrigan, undated; cuid17261; 449780 (Box 74, Cassette 154)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Political Theory and Ideology, undated; cuid17262; 449781 (Box 74, Cassette 155)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on the State and the Individual / Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Human Nature, undated; cuid17263; 449782 (Box 74, Cassette 156)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Tactics (Tape 1) / Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Women's Suffrage, undated; cuid17264; 449783 (Box 74, Cassette 157)
    - Howard Zinn: Interview with David Barsamian, undated; cuid17265; 449784 (Box 74, Cassette 158)
    - Howard Zinn and Studs Terkel in Discussion: Introduced by Alice Walker (Berkeley, CA), undated; cuid17266; 449785 (Box 74, Cassette 159)
    - Howard Zinn and Studs Terkel in Discussion: Introduced by Alice Walker (edited, Berkeley, CA), undated; cuid17267; 449786 (Box 74, Cassette 160)
    - Howard Zinn: Unidentified [Microcassette], undated; cuid17268; 449787 (Box 74, Cassette 161)
    - Marx in Soho by Howard Zinn (performed by Hal Fuller, directed by [Don Devecio]), undated; cuid17269; 449788 (Box 74, Cassette 162)
    - Marx in Soho by Howard Zinn: Performance in Italian, undated; cuid17270; 449789 (Box 74, Cassette 163)
    - New Hampshire Public Radio: Howard Zinn - Interview (edited), undated; cuid17271; 449790 (Box 74, Cassette 164)
    - New Hampshire Public Radio: Howard Zinn - Interview (edited), undated; cuid17272; 449791 (Box 74, Cassette 164 dup)
  - Subseries X:B: Audio Compact Disks, 1968-2009; 449282
    - Rev. Daniel Berrigan and Howard Zinn: Hanoi: Release of US Airmen (transfer from tape), 1968; cuid17273; 449792 (Box 75, Cd 165)
    - Howard Zinn at Maryville College, Fall 1969; cuid17274; 449793 (Box 75, Cd 166)
    - Howard Zinn's Last Class at Boston University, 1988; cuid17275; 449794 (Box 75, Cd 167)
    - Howard Zinn: "A People's History of the United States, A Lecture at Reed College" (AK Press Studio), 1998; cuid17276; 449795 (Box 75, Cd 168)
    - Howard Zinn: "A People's History of the United States, A Lecture at Reed College" (AK Press Studio), 1998; cuid17277; 449796 (Box 75, Cd 168 dup)
    - Noam Chomsky, Jimmy Tingle, Howard Zinn: "An Evening of Conversation, Confrontation and Comedy, A Benefit for Wellfleet Harbor Actors Theater", Aug 3, 2001; cuid17278; 449797 (Box 75, Cd 169)
    - Howard Zinn: "Heroes and Martyrs-Emma Goldman, Sacco and Vanzetti, and the Revolutionary Struggle" (AK Press Studio), 2001; cuid17279; 449798 (Box 75, Cd 170)
    - Howard Zinn: "Stories Hollywood Never Tells Us" (AK Press Studio), 2001; cuid17280; 449799 (Box 75, Cd 171)
    - Noam Chomsky and Howard Zinn (Photo CD), 2001-2002; cuid17281; 449800 (Box 75, Cd 172)
    - Howard Zinn: "Terrorism and War", Jun 17, 2002; cuid17282; 449801 (Box 75, Cd 173)
    - Howard Zinn: "Artists in a Time of War" (AK Press Audio), 2002; cuid17283; 449802 (Box 75, Cd 174)
    - Howard Zinn: "Civics Education: Patriotism of Skepticism" NPR's Justice Talking (The Annenberg Public Policy Center, University of Pennsylvania), 2002; cuid17284; 449803 (Box 75, Cd 175)
    - " A People's History of the United States, Highlights from the Twentieth Century" Read by Howard Zinn and Matt Damon (Harper Collins Publishers, Inc.) 4 CD set, 2002; cuid17285; 449807 (Box 75, Cd 177)
    - Howard Zinn (Photo CD), 2002-2008; cuid17286; 449808 (Box 75, Cd 178)
    - Howard Zinn: "USA and the War: Historic Perspective" (The Palestinian Radio Show at CKUT, 90.3 FM, Montreal, Quebec), Jan 20, 2003; cuid17287; 449809 (Box 75, Cd 179)
    - Howard Zinn Tribute - Voices from A People's History (92nd Street Y, New York City), Feb 23, 2003; cuid17288; 449810 (Box 75, Cd 180)
    - Howard Zinn: "History and War on Iraq" (Global Voices for Justice), Nov 3, 2003; cuid17289; 449811 (Box 75, Cd 181)
    - Howard Zinn: "Free and Fair" (KAOS, 89.2 FM, Olympia, WA), Dec 5, 2003; cuid17290; 449812 (Box 75, Cd 182)
    - Howard Zinn: "A Personal History" (Commonwealth Journal, Produced by WUMB Radio, University of Massachusetts, Boston), 2003; cuid17291; 449813 (Box 75, Cd 183)
    - Howard Zinn: "Why Civil Disobedience Matters" (KUCI, 88.9 FM, Irvine CA, Program "Justice or Just Us"), [2003]; cuid17292; 449814 (Box 75, Cd 184)
    - Howard Zinn: "Artists in Times of War" (Cambridge Forum Radio), Jan 21, 2004; cuid17293; 449815 (Box 75, Cd 185)
    - Howard Zinn and Noam Chomsky: "Is There Hope in this Desperate Time?" (Radio Free Maine), Sep 27, 2004; cuid17294; 449816 (Box 75, Cd 186)
    - "The Outsider in American Politics" from the Marc Steiner Show "America's Future: 2004" (88.1 WYPR, Baltimore MD), Oct 7, 2004; cuid17295; 449817 (Box 75, Cd 187)
    - Howard Zinn et al: "Voices from a People's History" (New York, NY, Alternative Radio) Part 1, Oct 22, 2004; cuid17296; 449818 (Box 75, Cd 188)
    - Howard Zinn et al: "Voices from a People's History" (New York, NY, Alternative Radio) Part 2, Oct 22, 2004; cuid17297; 449819 (Box 75, Cd 189)
    - "Voices of a People's History": New York Society of Ethical Culture (2 CD set), Oct 22, 2004; cuid17298; 449820 (Box 75, Cd 190)
    - Howard Zinn: "Class and War in U.S. Society, A Critique" (Maxve Societal Press), Oct 27, 2004; cuid17299; 449821 (Box 75, Cd 191)
    - Howard Zinn: "Empire, Resistance and the War in Iraq" (Keynote Speech, Historians Against the War Conference, Austin, TX) Disk 1, Feb 17, 2006; cuid17300; 449822 (Box 75, Cd 192)
    - Howard Zinn and Anthony Arnove: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" (Lannan Readings and Conversations) Disk 2 of 2, Apr 26, 2006; cuid17301; 449823 (Box 75, Cd 193)
    - Howard Zinn: "The Inner Life of Democracy" (Cambridge Forum Radio), Oct 25, 2006; cuid17302; 449824 (Box 75, Cd 194)
    - Howard Zinn: "Overcoming Obstacles" (Boulder, CO, Alternative Radio), Nov 30, 2006; cuid17303; 449825 (Box 75, Cd 195)
    - Howard Zinn: "Overcoming Obstacles" (Boulder, CO Alternative Radio), Nov 30, 2006; cuid17304; 449826 (Box 75, Cd 195 dup)
    - "Readings from Voices of a People's History of the United States," (Seven Stories Press), 2006; cuid17305; 449827 (Box 75, Cd 196)
    - Performance of Marx in Soho with Robert Weick, Feb 15, 2007; cuid17306; 449828 (Box 75, Cd 197)
    - Howard Zinn: Question and Answer Session after Performance of Marx in Soho, Feb 15, 2007; cuid17307; 449829 (Box 75, Cd 198)
    - "Rebel Voices" Performances (stage adaptation of Voices of A People's History of the United States), Dec 11, 2007, Dec 16, 2007; cuid17308; 449830 (Box 75, Cd 199)
    - Howard Zinn: "Reflections on War" (Commonwealth Journal, Prodcued by WUMB Radio, University of Massachusetts, Boston), 2007; cuid17309; 449831 (Box 75, Cd 200)
    - Howard Zinn Readings (Photo CD), Jan 8, 2008; cuid17310; 449832 (Box 75, Cd 201)
    - "America, Empire of Liberty": Panel Discussion (Howard Zinn participating) on BBC Radio, Sep 2008; cuid17311; 449833 (Box 75, Cd 202)
    - "Sacco and Vanzetti 08" (companion piece to news report from Boston about Anarchists marking the 81st Anniversary of the execution of Sacco and Vanzetti), 2008; cuid17312; 449834 (Box 75, Cd 203)
    - "Living with the Consequences, The Legacy of the U.S. Policy in Nicaragua" (Photos of Page Proofs for Book) Part 1, [2008]; cuid17313; 449835 (Box 75, Cd 204)
    - "Living with the Consequences, The Legacy of the U.S. Policy in Nicaragua" (Photos of Page Proofs for Book) Part 2, [2008]; cuid17314; 449836 (Box 75, Cd 205)
    - "Americans Who Tell the Truth (and other recent Social Justice reports produced by Chuck U. Rosina)", Jan 2009-Apr 2009; cuid17315; 449837 (Box 75, Cd 206)
    - Marx a Roma Radio Performance (Also second disk that includes 2 bitmap images and an MP3 file), Jun 2009; cuid17316; 449838 (Box 75, Cd 207)
    - Marx in Soho Music Compilation, undated; cuid17317; 449839 (Box 75, Cd 208)
    - Emma Act 2 Scenes 13-15, undated; cuid17318; 449840 (Box 75, Cd 209)
    - Rossi Interview with Zinn (in Italian), undated; cuid17319; 449841 (Box 75, Cd 210)
  - Subseries X:C: Audio Reel-to-Reel, 1957-1975; 449283
    - Howard Zinn: Spanish-American War, (Denver CO, 5 Inch), Jul 16, 1957; cuid17320; 449845 (Box 76, Reel 211)
    - Panel Discussion with Spelman College's First Exchange Students: Includes Sharon Passow, Mary Millen, Martha Thiessen, Mary Anne Peterson, Jackee Walken, May 1960; cuid17321; 449846 (Box 76, Reel 212)
    - Sit-In Showdown: Includes Music, Dance Performance and Comedy Tape 1, May 17, 1960; cuid17322; 449847 (Box 76, Reel 213)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): "China: Past and Present", "East and West", Lecture on Confucianism, Discussion of Menicus and Hsun-tze, Sep 26, 1961; cuid17323; 449848 (Box 76, Reel 214)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Session on the Chinese Language, Sep 27, 1961; cuid17324; 449849 (Box 76, Reel 215)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): "China: Past and Present," "Legalism and Confucianism" (also includes Hocking seminar on Confucianism), Sep 30, 1961; cuid17325; 449850 (Box 76, Reel 216)
    - Meet the Press: Ambassador Tsiang on Nationalist China / Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Chinese History, Oct 8, 1961/Oct 10, 1961; cuid17326; 449851 (Box 76, Reel 217)
    - Martin Luther King Jr. at Town Hall Meeting on Non-Violence (Atlanta University, GA) / Radio Broadcast: "The South: 1961" (Baptist Revival), Oct 12, 1961/Nov 12, 1961; cuid17327; 449852 (Box 86, Box 76, Reel 218)
      Access Copies
      An access copy of this recording (3 CDs) is available in box 86 of this collection.
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Owen Lattimore on China and Outer Mongolia, Oct 18, 1961; cuid17328; 449853 (Box 76, Reel 219)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Derk Bodde on Confucian Thought and Legal System, Nov 7, 1961; cuid17329; 449854 (Box 76, Reel 220)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Public Lecture - Derk Bodde on Old Society and New Forces, Nov 8, 1961; cuid17330; 449855 (Box 76, Reel 221)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Carl Holman and Elsie Edmondson on Chinese Literature, Nov 14, 1961; cuid17331; 449856 (Box 76, Reel 222)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Thomas Alitzer and Josephus Coan on Buddhism and Chinese Religion, Nov 28, 1961; cuid17332; 449857 (Box 76, Reel 223)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Alan Kagan on Chinese Music, Dec 12, 1961; cuid17333; 449858 (Box 76, Reel 224)
    - Domenico Scarlatti: Sonatas in E Major, G Minor and D Minor (5 Inch), Dec 24, 1961; cuid17334; 449859 (Box 76, Reel 225)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - "The Western Impact on China" (Kennedy, Duncan, and Rowley), Jan 2, 1962; cuid17335; 449860 (Box 76, Reel 226)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Benjamin Schwartz on China's Response to the West, Jan 9, 1962; cuid17336; 449861 (Box 76, Reel 227)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Jon Johnston on the Meeting of East and West, Jan 16, 1962; cuid17337; 449862 (Box 76, Reel 228)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Bingham Duncan and Howard Zinn on the Background of the 1911 Revolution, Feb 20, 1962; cuid17338; 449863 (Box 76, Reel 229)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Chet Huntley on NBC White Paper on China, Feb 25, 1962; cuid17339; 449864 (Box 76, Reel 230)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Howard Zinn on the May 4th Movement and the Rise of Communism, Feb 27, 1962; cuid17340; 449865 (Box 76, Reel 231)
    - Informal Discussion with Exchange Students at the Zinn House, Feb 1962; cuid17341; 449866 (Box 86, Box 76, Reel 232)
      An access copy of this recording (4 CDs) is available in box 86 of this collection.
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): John K. Fairbank Lecture, Mar 6, 1962; cuid17342; 449867 (Box 77, Reel 233)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Howard Zinn on Marxist Theory, Mar 13, 1962; cuid17343; 449868 (Box 77, Reel 234, Box 86)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      An access copy of this recording (2 CDs) is available in box 86 of this collection.
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Howard Zinn on Communist Theory, Mar 20, 1962; cuid17344; 449869 (Box 77, Reel 235)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Harry Steinmetz and Robert Cole on Thought Reform, Mar 27, 1962; cuid17345; 449870 (Box 77, Reel 236)
    - Robert Williams: Interviewed by March Schleiffer in Havana, Cuba (Broadcast Jun 5, 1962), Mar 1962; cuid17346; 449871 (Box 77, Reel 237)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Dr. Anthony Stampolis on the Economy of Communist China, Apr 5, 1962; cuid17347; 449872 (Box 77, Reel 238)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Herbert Ross and Carl Hollman on the Family in Communist China, Apr 10, 1962; cuid17348; 449873 (Box 77, Reel 239)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Ping-chia Kuo Lecture, Apr 17, 1962; cuid17349; 449874 (Box 77, Reel 240)
    - Richard Starr: Lecture on China and the Soviet Bloc, May 1, 1962; cuid17350; 449875 (Box 77, Reel 241)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar on China (includes William Worthy, Allan Cole, and Richard Walker), May 9, 1962; cuid17351; 449876 (Box 77, Reel 242)
    - Chris Allen in Dawson / Terrell, Sep 27, 1962; cuid17352; 449877 (Box 77, Reel 243)
    - Discussion with Young Unitarians: Staughton Lynd and Alice Walker, Oct 1962; cuid17353; 449878 (Box 86, Box 77, Reel 244)
      Access Copy
      An access copy of this recording (1 CD) is available in box 86 of this collection.
    - Lecture on Food Aid for China [Preview of Television Documentary], 1962; cuid17354; 449879 (Box 77, Reel 245)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Exchange Students in USSR (Includes Ed Morrell, Dick Judy and Mark Mancall), cuid17355; 449880 (Box 77, Reel 246)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Speak Chinese, Lessons 1-6 and Revised Lessons 1-6 (Institute of Far Eastern Languages, Yale University), cuid17356; 449881 (Box 77, Reel 247)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Speak Chinese, Lessons 7-15 (Institute of Far Eastern Languages, Yale University), cuid17357; 449882 (Box 77, Reel 248)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Speak Chinese, Lessons 16-22 (Institute of Far Eastern Languages, Yale University), cuid17358; 449883 (Box 77, Reel 249)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Speak Chinese, Lessons 23-24 and Vocabulary Review Lessons 1-24 (Institute of Far Eastern Languages, Yale University), cuid17359; 449884 (Box 77, Reel 250)
    - Young Americans for Freedom: Debate - Shall the House Committee on Un-American Activities be Abolished? (includes Fulton Lewis III, Howard Zinn and Nancy Perkins, Emory University, Atlanta GA), Feb 11, 1963; cuid17360; 449885 (Box 77, Reel 251, Box 86)
    - Social Science Club Meeting: Liberty and Spelman College (Darcas Bait, Chairman) Tape 1, Mar 11, 1963; cuid17361; 449886 (Box 77, Reel 252, Box 86)
    - Social Science Club Meeting: Liberty and Spelman College (Darcas Bait, Chairman) Tape 2, Mar 11, 1963; cuid17362; 449887 (Box 77, Reel 253, Box 86)
    - Social Science Club Meeting: Liberty and Spelman College (Darcas Bait, Chairman) Tape 3, Mar 11, 1963; cuid17363; 449888 (Box 77, Reel 254, Box 86)
    - Town Meeting: What Should We Do About Cuba?: Includes Staughton Lynd, Robert Brisbane and Robert Trucker (Atlanta University, GA), Mar 21, 1963; cuid17364; 449889 (Box 78, Reel 255)
    - Meeting: Includes Mrs. Pilcher, John Novack and Paul Jourdan (Greenwood, MS), Aug 15, 1963; cuid17365; 449890 (Box 78, Reel 256)
    - Meeting: Includes Kids from County Jail and Marchman (Greenwood, MS), Aug 16, 1963; cuid17366; 449891 (Box 78, Reel 257)
    - Stokely Carmichael: Lecture (Greenwood, MS), Aug 1963; cuid17367; 449892 (Box 78, Reel 258)
    - Interview Conducted by Howard Zinn with SNCC Workers (Selma, AL) / [Bruce Bovington] Interviewed by Alan Ribback, Oct 6, 1963/Sep 29, 1963; cuid17368; 449893 (Box 86, Box 78, Reel 259)
    - Malcolm X: Message to the Grass Roots (King Solomon Baptist Church, Detroit, MI 5 Inch), [Nov 10, 1963]; cuid17369; 449894 (Box 78, Reel 260)
    - Interview with Charlie Cogg, SNCC / Singing at Staff Meeting (Greenville, MS), Nov 14, 1963; cuid17370; 449895 (Box 78, Reel 261)
    - SNCC Washington Conference: Food and Jobs (Saturday Evening Dinner), Dec 1, 1963; cuid17371; 449896 (Box 78, Reel 262)
    - SNCC Washington Conference: Government Agencies, Dec 1, 1963; cuid17372; 449897 (Box 78, Reel 263)
    - SNCC Washington Conference: Bayard Rustin Speech, Dec 1, 1963; cuid17373; 449898 (Box 86, Box 78, Reel 264)
    - SNCC Washington Conference: Bob Moses on Life article on SNCC / TV Program NET on White Northerners and Segregation, Dec 1, 1963/Dec 2, 1963; cuid17374; 449899 (Box 78, Reel 265, Box 86, Cd 1)
    - Southern Report on Police Brutality (Gasden, AL 5 Inch), 1963; cuid17375; 449900 (Box 78, Reel 266)
    - Edgar Snow: Lecture on China (Guest Lecturer in Howard Zinn's Class), 1963; cuid17376; 449901 (Box 86, Box 78, Reel 267)
    - Howard Zinn: Speech Haverford College (Haverford, PA), Feb 1964; cuid17377; 449902 (Box 78, Reel 268, Box 86)
    - NBC-TV Program on James Chaney, Andrew Goodman and Michael Schwerner (Murdered Mississippi Civil Rights Workers), Jun 27, 1964; cuid17378; 449903 (Box 78, Reel 269)
    - National Archives and Records Service: Lyndon B. Johnson - Remarks at Syracuse University on the Communist Challenge in Southeast Asia, Aug 5, 1964; cuid17379; 452466 (Box 78, Reel 270)
    - Howard Zinn: Interview on SNCC, The New Abolitionists and The Southern Mystique, [1964]; cuid17380; 449904 (Box 78, Reel 271)
    - Vietnam Debate: McGeorge Bundy vs Hans Morgenthau, Jun 1965; cuid17381; 452467 (Box 78, Reel 272)
    - National Archives and Records Service: Lyndon B. Johnson - State of the Union Address Part 1, Jan 12, 1966; cuid17382; 449905 (Box 78, Reel 273)
    - National Archives and Records Service: Lyndon B. Johnson - State of the Union Address Part 2, Jan 12, 1966; cuid17383; 449906 (Box 78, Reel 274)
    - Dean Rusk: Speech (Indiana University, IN), Oct 31, 1967; cuid17384; 449907 (Box 78, Reel 275)
    - WFIU: Howard Zinn - Convocation Address on the Necessity of Immediate Withdrawal from Vietnam (Indiana University, Bloomington, IN) Tape 1, Dec 1, 1967; cuid17385; 449908 (Box 78, Reel 276)
    - WFIU: Howard Zinn - Convocation Address on the Necessity of Immediate Withdrawl from Vietnam (Indiana University, Bloomington, IN) Tape 2, Dec 1, 1967; cuid17386; 449909 (Box 78, Reel 277)
    - National Archives and Records Service: Lyndon B. Johnson - Address to the American People (Master), Mar 31, 1968; cuid17387; 449910 (Box 79, Reel 278)
    - National Archives and Records Service: Lyndon B. Johnson - Address to the American People (Copy), Mar 31, 1968; cuid17388; 449911 (Box 79, Reel 279)
    - WDET: Howard Zinn - "Abolitionist Motivations: Pro and Con" (Wayne State University Centennial, Detroit, MI), 1968; cuid17389; 449916 (Box 79, Reel 280)
    - WHPK: Marlene Dixon Press Conference on University of Chicago's Decision Not to Rehire her (Includes Sit-In, 10 1/2 Inches), Feb 12, 1969; cuid17390; 449914 (Box 79, Reel 281)
    - Abbie Hoffman (Harvard University Cambridge, MA), Fall 1969; cuid17391; 449915 (Box 79, Reel 282)
    - Howard Zinn: Speech (Moratorium to End the War in Vietnam Day), Oct 15, 1969; cuid17392; 449913 (Box 79, Reel 283, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref2163)
      Duration: 26 min.
    - National Archives and Record Service: Richard Nixon - Address to the Nation on the War in Vietnam, Nov 3, 1969; cuid17393; 449917 (Box 79, Reel 284)
    - National Archives and Record Service: Recording of the Demonstration and Shooting at Kent State by Steve Titchenal (played at Public Hearings in Kent, Ohio, Aug 19 and 21, 1970), May 4, 1970; cuid17394; 449918 (Box 79, Reel 285)